<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipes Thai Restaurant</string>

    <!--    Food    -->
    <string name="Title_food_1">khao niew mamuang
        <!--        (mango sticky rice)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_1">
        1 1/2 cups glutinous (sweet) rice.\n
        1 1/3 cups well-stirred canned unsweetened coconut milk. \n
        1/3 cup plus 3 tablespoons sugar. \n
        1/4 teaspoon salt. \n
        1 tablespoon sesame seeds, toasted lightly. \n
        1 large mango, peeled, pitted, and cut into thin slices (at least 24).
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_1">
        In a bowl wash rice well in several changes of cold water until water is clear. \n
        Soak rice in cold water to cover overnight. \n
        Drain rice well in a sieve. \n
        Set sieve over a large deep saucepan of simmering water (sieve should not touch water) and steam rice, covered with a kitchen towel and a lid, 30 to 40 minutes, or until tender (check water level in pan occasionally, adding more water if necessary). \n
        While rice is cooking, in a small saucepan bring 1 cup coconut milk to a boil with 1/3 cup sugar and salt, stirring until sugar is dissolved, and remove from heat. \n
        Keep mixture warm. \n
        Transfer cooked rice to a bowl and stir in coconut-milk mixture. \n
        Let rice stand, covered, 30 minutes, or until coconut-milk mixture is absorbed. \n
        Rice may be prepared up to this point 2 hours ahead and kept covered at room temperature. \n
        While rice is standing, in cleaned small pan slowly boil remaining 1/3 cup coconut milk with remaining 3 tablespoons sugar, stirring occasionally, 1 minute. \n
        Transfer sauce to a small bowl and chill until cool and thickened slightly. \n
        To serve, mold 1/4 cup servings of sticky rice on dessert plates. \n
        Drizzle desserts with sauce and sprinkle with sesame seeds. \n
        Divide mango slices among plates.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_2">khao phat or khao pad
        <!--        (fried rice)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_2">
        1 tablespoon oil.
        \n
        1/2 pound boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into small pieces.
        \n
        1 medium onion, diced.
        \n
        4 cups bok choy, sliced.
        \n
        2 cloves garlic, chopped.
        \n
        1/2 cup peas (fresh or frozen).
        \n
        1/2 cup shredded carrot.
        \n
        4 cups cooked brown jasmine rice.
        \n
        2 eggs, lightly beaten.
        \n
        1 tablespoon fish sauce.
        \n
        1 tablespoon reduced-sodium soy sauce.
        \n
        1 tablespoon Sriracha.
        \n
        1 tablespoon lime juice.
        \n
        2 green onions, sliced.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_2">
        Heat a large wok or pan over medium-high heat, add the chicken, onions and the thick white parts of the bok choy and stir-fry until the chicken is almost cooked, 2-3 minutes.
        \n
        Add the garlic, peas and carrots and stir-fry for 2 minutes.
        \n
        Add the rice and remaining bok choy and stir-fry, while mixing, for 2 minutes.
        \n
        Make a well in the middle of the pan; add the eggs and let them sit for a minute before scrambling and mixing them into the ingredients in the wok.
        \n
        Cook for another 2 minutes.
        \n
        Add in the fish sauce, soy sauce, Sriracha and lime juice along with the green onions and remove from heat.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_3">guay teow
        <!--        (noodle soup)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_3">
        65 grams vital wheat gluten. \n
        18 grams tapioca starch (2 tablespoons). \n
        ⅛ teaspoon ground white pepper. \n
        Pinch sugar. \n
        Pinch MSG. \n
        30 millilitres cold water (2 tablespoons). \n
        15 millilitres vegetable oil (1 tablespoon). \n
        10 millilitres white rice vinegar (2 teaspoons). \n
        10 millilitres Thai thin soy sauce (2 teaspoons).
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_3">
        Whisk dry ingredients together in a medium bowl. \n
        Combine remaining ingredients in a small bowl. \n
        Pour into flour and stir with your fingers until it comes together, just beyond shaggy. \n
        Leave to rest for 10 minutes. \n
        Heat a small pot of water on low, not boiling. \n
        When hot, tear the seitan pieces into the size you’d like and add them to the water. \n
        Cook for 10 minutes and drain.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_4">tom yum goong
        <!--        (spicy shrimp soup)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_4">
        1 ½ pounds medium shrimp.
         \n
        9 ½ cups water, divided.
         \n
        ½ cup chopped peeled fresh galangal (about 2 ounces).
         \n
        ½ cup (2-inch) pieces peeled fresh lemongrass (about 4 stalks).
         \n
        6 fresh or frozen kaffir lime leaves.
         \n
        ½ cup canned straw mushrooms, quartered.
         \n
        2 tablespoons roasted red chili paste (such as Thai Kitchen).
         \n
        1 tablespoon fish sauce.
         \n
        2 Thai chiles.
         \n
        ½ cup chopped green onions.
         \n
        ½ cup chopped fresh cilantro.
         \n
        1 tablespoon fresh lime juice.
         \n
        6 tablespoons chopped dry-roasted unsalted peanuts.
         \n
        4 lime wedges
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_4">
        Peel and devein shrimp, reserving shells.
         \n
        Combine shrimp shells and 6 cups water in a Dutch oven; bring to a simmer.
         \n
        Cook 1 hour.
         \n
        Strain broth through a sieve into a bowl; discard solids.
         \n
        Combine broth and remaining 3 1/2 cups water in a large saucepan; bring to a boil.
         \n
        Add galangal, lemongrass, and kaffir lime leaves to pan; simmer 10 minutes.
         \n
        Strain broth mixture through a sieve into a bowl; discard solids.
         \n
        Return broth mixture to pan. Add mushrooms, chili paste, fish sauce, and chiles; bring to a boil.
         \n
        Stir in shrimp, green onions, and cilantro; cook 3 minutes or until shrimp are done.
         \n
        Discard chiles.
         \n
        Stir in fresh lime juice.
         \n
        Ladle 2 cups soup into each of 4 bowls; sprinkle evenly with peanuts.
         \n
        Serve with lime wedges.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_5">khao soi
        <!--        (cream ycoconut curry noodle soup)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_5">
        2 cups chicken broth no sodium preferred.
         \n
        14 oz coconut milk 1 can.
         \n
        1-2 tbsp Thai red curry paste.
         \n
        1/2 inch ginger thinly sliced.
         \n
        2 cloves garlic crushed.
         \n
        1 large chicken breast or 2 small ones.
         \n
        1 tbsp fish sauce or to taste.
         \n
        1 tbsp sugar or to taste, brown sugar preferred.
         \n
        2 portions egg noodles or ramen noodles.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_5">
        In the Instant Pot insert, add the chicken stock, coconut milk, red curry paste, garlic, ginger, and chicken breast.
         \n
        Cook on high pressure for 5 minutes.
         \n
        While the Instant Pot is doing it’s thing, slice the shallots, cut the lime, and wash the cilantro.
         \n
        If you’re using any extra toppings, prep them now. Cook and drain your noodles and divide them between two deep bowls.
         \n
        When the Instant Pot is done, quick release the pressure.
         \n
        Carefully remove the chicken and shred.
         \n
        Add the chicken to the bowls with the noodles.
         \n
        Stir the fish sauce and brown sugar into the soup.
         \n
        Taste the soup and adjust the seasoning with fish sauce, sugar, and curry paste if needed, then divide evenly between the two bowls.
         \n
        Finish with lime and cilantro and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_6">tom kha gai
        <!--        (chicken in coconut soup)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_6">
        1 1” piece ginger, peeled.
         \n
        10 makrut (Thai) lime leaves or 1 Tbsp. lime zest and ¼ cup lime juice.
         \n
        6 cups low-sodium chicken broth.
         \n
        1½ lb. skinless, boneless chicken thighs, cut into 1” pieces.
         \n
        8 oz. shiitake, oyster, or maitake mushrooms, stemmed, caps cut into bite-size pieces.
         \n
        1 13.5-oz. can coconut milk.
         \n
        2 Tbsp. fish sauce (such as nam pla or nuoc nam).
         \n
        1 tsp. sugar.
         \n
        2 stalks fresh lemongrass, tough outer layers removed.
         \n
        Chili oil, cilantro leaves with tender stems, and lime wedges (for serving).
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_6">
        Using the back of a knife, lightly smash lemongrass and ginger; cut lemongrass into 4” pieces.
         \n
        Bring lemongrass, ginger, lime leaves, and broth to a boil in a large saucepan.
         \n
        Reduce heat and simmer until flavors are melded, 8–10 minutes.
         \n
        Strain broth into clean saucepan; discard solids.
         \n
        Add chicken and return to a boil. Reduce heat, add mushrooms, and simmer, skimming occasionally, until chicken is cooked through and mushrooms are soft, 20–25 minutes.
         \n
        Mix in coconut milk, fish sauce, and sugar.
         \n
        Divide soup among bowls.
         \n
        Serve with chili oil, cilantro, and lime wedges.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_7">pad see eiw
        <!--        (thick noodle dish)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_7">
        8 ounces extra wide rice noodles.
         \n
        2 chicken breasts boneless and skinless.
         \n
        1/4 cup canola oil divided.
         \n
        3 tablespoons light soy sauce.
         \n
        1 tablespoon dark soy sauce.
         \n
        2 teaspoons fish sauce.
         \n
        2 tablespoons oyster sauce.
         \n
        1 tablespoon sugar.
         \n
        1 egg scrambled.
         \n
        3 cloves garlic minced.
         \n
        3 cups broccoli florets.
         \n
        8 ounces sliced mushrooms.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_7">
        Soak the noodles for 30 minutes in cold water or boil them for one minute and steep them in the hot water for five minutes before draining.
         \n
        Cut the chicken into thin strips and toss with soy sauce.
         \n
        Add 2 tablespoons of canola oil to the wok or large skillet on medium high heat.
         \n
        Sear the chicken on both sides for 2-3 minutes.
         \n
        While the chicken is cooking add the soy sauce, dark soy sauce, fish sauce and oyster sauce to a bowl and whisk them together.
         \n
        Add in the egg to the skillet and chop it up with a spatula while cooking.
         \n
        Add in the garlic, broccoli and mushrooms with the remaining oil.
         \n
        Cook on high heat before adding in the noodles and chicken.
         \n
        Cook the noodles until slightly crispy 2-3 minutes.
         \n
        Add in the sauce, toss well and let cook for another 1-2 minutes or until noodles caramelize a little.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_8">pad thai
        <!--        (stir fried noodles)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_8">
        8 ounces/220 g Thai rice noodles.
         \n
        1/2 pound chicken breasts (or thighs, chopped into bite-size pieces).
         \n
        3 cloves garlic, minced.
         \n
        1/4 cup grated carrot or cabbage.
         \n
        1 egg.
         \n
        1/3 cup crushed or roughly chopped peanuts or cashews.
         \n
        2 green onions (thinly sliced).
         \n
        2 cups fresh bean sprouts.
         \n
        1 handful fresh basil.
         \n
        1/4 cup dry-roasted peanuts (or cashews, unsalted).
         \n
        2 tablespoons vegetable oil.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_8">
        Gather the ingredients.
         \n
        Boil rice noodles until too tough to serve but soft enough to eat, a firm "al dente" (noodles will finish cooking when you fry them so avoid overcooking at this point).
         \n
        Drain, and rinse with cold water to keep from sticking.
         \n
        Combine all "stir-fry sauce" ingredients together in a cup.
         \n
        Drizzle 2 tablespoons of sauce over the chopped chicken, and stir.
         \n
        Heat a wok or large non-stick frying pan over medium-high heat.
         \n
        Drizzle in oil, and swirl around then add garlic.
         \n
        Stir fry 1 minute.
         \n
        Add chicken, and stir fry 2 minutes.
         \n
        Add carrot or cabbage, drizzling a little more stir-fry sauce into the pan if it becomes dry.
         \n
        Push ingredients aside, and crack the egg into the middle.
         \n
        Scramble quickly, and incorporate with other ingredients.
         \n
        Add noodles and 1/4 of the stir-fry sauce, using two utensils to lift and turn them in the pan.
         \n
        Stir fry 30 seconds, and add more sauce, continuing in this way until most of the sauce has been used.
         \n
        Add bean sprouts and continue stir frying another 2 to 3 minutes.
         \n
        Taste test and add remaining sauce if you would like more flavor.
         \n
        Add a little more fish sauce for even greater depth of flavor.
         \n
        Serve topped with chopped nuts, spring onion, and fresh basil.
         \n
        Garnish with lime wedges and squeeze over just before eating.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_9">pad kee mao
        <!--        (drunken noodles)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_9">
        Produce: shallots, carrots, garlic, fresh ginger, zucchini, bell pepper, green onions, roma tomatoes, basil.
         \n
        Rice noodles.
         \n
        Sesame oil (or canola).
         \n
        Chicken (or other protein).
         \n
        Sauce ingredients: oyster sauce, soy sauce, fish sauce, brown sugar, water, red chili sauce.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_9">
        Cook the rice noodles according to package instructions. Drain, rinse with with water and set aside.
         \n
        Prepare the sauce:  Mix sauce ingredients in a small bowl.
         \n
        Cook chicken and vegetables.
         \n
        Heat oil in wok or large skillet over high heat.
         \n
        Add shallots and carrot and cook for 2 minutes.
         \n
        Add more oil and cook chicken.
         \n
        Add garlic and ginger, add bell pepper, zucchini, and the whites of the chopped green onion and sauté.
         \n
        Add noodles and sauce.
         \n
        Toss and cook for a few minutes until warmed through.
         \n
        Remove from heat and stir in chopped basil.
         \n
        Serve immediately, garnished with remaining green onion and extra chili sauce, sriracha, or crushed red pepper, for added spice.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_food_10">laab
        <!--        (spicy salad)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_10">
        Rice powder:
         \n
            ½ cup water.
             \n
            2 tablespoons uncooked long-grain Thai sticky rice.
         \n
        Marinade:
         \n
            1 teaspoon white peppercorns.
             \n
            1 teaspoon kosher or sea salt.
             \n
            6 garlic cloves, minced.
             \n
            1 (6-ounce) can pineapple juice.
             \n
            1 ½ pounds boneless sirloin steak, trimmed.
             \n
            Cooking spray.
         \n
        Remaining ingredients:
         \n
            3 tablespoons fresh lime juice.
             \n
            1 cup torn fresh mint.
             \n
            ⅓ cup coarsely chopped fresh cilantro leaves.
             \n
            ¼ cup minced shallots.
             \n
            3 tablespoons thinly sliced green onions.
             \n
            2 tablespoons Thai fish sauce.
             \n
            1 tablespoon crushed red pepper.
             \n
            1 tablespoon thinly sliced kaffir lime leaves (about 8 leaves) or 1 grated lime rind.
             \n
            1 teaspoon minced bird chile or 2 s minced serrano chile.
             \n
            ½ teaspoon kosher or sea salt.
             \n
            12 tender napa (Chinese) cabbage leaves or any sturdy lettuce leaves.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_10">
        To prepare rice powder, combine water and rice in a bowl.
         \n
        Let stand 1 hour.
         \n
        Drain and rinse rice with cold water; pat dry.
         \n
        Cook rice in a small nonstick skillet over medium-high heat 7 minutes, stirring constantly until lightly browned.
         \n
        Cool completely.
         \n
        Place rice in a spice or coffee grinder; process until rice resembles cornmeal.
         \n
        Set aside.
         \n
        To prepare marinade, place peppercorns in pan over medium-high heat, and cook for 3 minutes, stirring constantly or until toasted.
         \n
        Place peppercorns in spice or coffee grinder; process until ground.
         \n
        Combine ground pepper, 1 teaspoon salt, garlic, pineapple juice, and the steak in a large zip-top plastic bag; seal and marinate in refrigerator 30 minutes.
         \n
        Preheat broiler.
         \n
        Remove steak from bag, reserving the marinade.
         \n
        Place steak on a broiler pan coated with cooking spray.
         \n
        Broil 16 minutes or until desired degree of doneness, turning and basting with reserved marinade after 8 minutes.
         \n
        Cut the steak diagonally across grain into thin slices.
        \n
        Cut slices crosswise into thin slivers.
         \n
        Combine steak and lime juice in a large bowl.
         \n
        Add rice powder, mint, and next 8 ingredients (mint through 1/2 teaspoon salt), and toss well.
         \n
        Spoon 1/3 cup steak mixture into each cabbage leaf.
          </string>

    <string name="Title_food_11">som tam
        <!--        (spicy green papaya salad)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_11">
        1 small green, unripe papaya.
         \n
        1 medium clove garlic, minced.
         \n
        1 small red chile pepper, such as Thai bird, seeded and finely chopped.
         \n
        2 tablespoons fish sauce, or soy sauce.
         \n
        2 tablespoons vegetable oil.
         \n
        3 tablespoons freshly squeezed lime juice.
         \n
        2 tablespoons brown sugar.
         \n
        5 large green beans.
         \n
        1 cup cherry tomatoes, halved.
         \n
        2 cups bean sprouts.
         \n
        1/4 cup coarsely chopped Thai or Italian basil, for garnish.
         \n
        1/2 cup roasted peanuts or cashews, for garnish.
         \n
        1/2 teaspoon granulated sugar, optional.
         \n
        3 medium scallions, thinly sliced lengthwise.
         \n
        Sticky rice for serving, optional.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_11">
        Gather the ingredients.
         \n
        Peel the green papaya.
         \n
        Using the largest grater you have (such as one for scalloped potatoes), grate the green fruit, rotating it as you go to avoid hitting the inner seeds.
         \n
        If you do not have a grater, try a method used in Thailand: First, deeply score the flesh using a large, sharp knife.
         \n
        Then, run your knife just under the surface to release the shreds.
         \n
        In a small food chopper or processor, add the garlic, chile pepper, fish sauce, oil, lime juice, and brown sugar.
         \n
        Process until the liquid turns reddish from the chile. Set this salad dressing aside.
         \n
        Alternatively, pound the garlic and chile into a fine paste with a mortar and pestle or with the back of a knife.
         \n
        Transfer to a small bowl, add the fish sauce, oil, lime juice, and brown sugar, and whisk to combine.
         \n
        Slice the green beans into segments and add them to the chopper or processor.
         \n
        Pulse to lightly chop and bruise the beans. In Thailand, the beans are pounded to bruise them, but this method works just as well.
         \n
        Place the shredded papaya, cherry tomatoes, and bean sprouts in a large salad bowl.
         \n
        Add most of the basil, holding back some to be used as a garnish.
         \n
        Add the chile dressing and beans and toss.
         \n
        Add most of the peanuts, holding some back to be used for garnish, and toss again.
         \n
        Test for taste and adjust the flavor of salad as desired.
         \n
        If you would like a more intense flavor or extra saltiness, add an extra splash of fish or soy sauce.
         \n
        More chile can be added to make it spicier.
         \n
        If it is too sour, sprinkle a little white sugar over your salad and toss to mix (the sugar will melt in a minute or two).
         \n
        Garnish with the scallions, and the remaining basil and peanuts.
         \n
        Serve your salad as is or as a side dish to any Thai entree.
         \n
        If this is your main course, try serving it with a side of sticky rice like they do in Thailand.
          </string>

    <string name="Title_food_12">yum pla duk foo
        <!--        (crispy catfish with green mango salad)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_food_12">
        1 catfish (400-500g, grilled) or any other medium-firm textured fish fillets such as tilapia, cod or haddock.
         \n
        ½ cup green mango (sliced into long thin slivers).
         \n
        2-3 shallots (sliced thinly).
         \n
        3 tbsp fish sauce.
         \n
        4 tbsp lime juice.
         \n
        1 tbsp sugar.
         \n
        2 tbsp palm sugar (finely chopped).
         \n
        1 tbsp dried shrimp ( chopped).
         \n
        4-5 bird’s eye chillies (mince a few for taste and slice the rest lengthwise for garnish).
         \n
        1 tsp coriander (optional or more, as garnish).
         \n
        ¼ cup peanuts or cashew nuts (toasted).
         \n
        ½-1 cup vegetable oil.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_food_12">
        Cut the fish into chunks, season with soy sauce or salt, then steam for 5 mins until the meat is fully cooked.
         \n
        Set the fish aside to cool.
         \n
        In the meantime, prepare the mango salad.
         \n
        In a mortar, pound 2-3 bird’s eye chillies until there are no big chunks, then add palm sugar and mash to a paste.
         \n
        Add fish sauce and lime juice and mix until sugar is completely dissolved.
         \n
        Transfer paste to a bowl and add the shallots, dried shrimp, and julienned mango.
         \n
        Set aside to sit while you fry the fish.
         \n
        Once the fish is cool, transfer it to a bowl lined with muslin cloth.
         \n
        Wrap the cloth around the fish, twist, and squeeze as hard as you can to remove as much liquid as possible.
         \n
        Then, transfer the fish to a mortar and pestle and pound it until it’s fluffy with no chunks left.
         \n
        In a wok or a large pot, heat about 3 cm of oil over high heat.
         \n
        Now to put the fu (fluffiness) in the fish, the oil has to be heated to about 200℃.
         \n
        Once the oil is hot enough, sprinkle half of the fish into the oil.
         \n
        Be careful as the oil will bubble aggressively.
         \n
        While the fish cooks, try to tuck the edges of the fish and push the fish down to submerge in oil to fry and brown evenly.
         \n
        Once fish is golden brown, remove from oil with a slotted skimmer and set it on paper towels to drain.
         \n
        Place the fish on a serving plate and sprinkle with roasted peanuts.
         \n
        Garnish mango salad with chopped coriander (optional) and serve beside the fish.
         \n
        Serve the yum pla duk foo as a snack or as a main dish with steamed rice.
          </string>


    <!--    Drinks    -->
    <string name="Title_drinks_1">cha yen
        <!--        (thai style tea)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_drinks_1">
        4 tablespoons loose red rooibos tea leaves (or the contents of 10 rooibos tea bags).
         \n
        3 tablespoons loose black tea leaves (or the contents of 7 black tea bags).
         \n
        3 tablespoons granulated sugar.
         \n
        10 star anise pods, broken into pieces or roughly chopped.
         \n
        10 whole cloves.
         \n
        ½ cup half-and-half.
         \n
        ½ cup sweetened condensed milk.
         \n
        1 tablespoon vanilla extract.
         \n
        Ice, for serving.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_drinks_1">
        Add 4 cups water to a medium saucepan.
         \n
        Cover with a lid and bring to a boil.
         \n
        Remove from the heat.
         \n
        Add rooibos tea, black tea, sugar, star anise and cloves; cover and let steep, 10 minutes.
         \n
        Strain tea, pressing on tea leaves and spices to extract as much liquid as possible, then discarding solids.
         \n
        Refrigerate tea until chilled, at least 1 hour.
         \n
        In a measuring glass, stir together the half-and-half, condensed milk and vanilla extract.
         \n
        Fill a pint glass with ice.
         \n
        Add 3/4 cup tea mixture and top with about 2½ tablespoons condensed milk mixture.
         \n
        Serve immediately.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_drinks_2">thai milk tea chayen </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_drinks_2">
        1 tablespoon Thai Tea Leaves.
         \n
        1 cup of of hot boiling water.
         \n
        2 teaspoons sugar.
         \n
        2 teaspoons sweetened condensed milk.
         \n
        2 teaspoons evaporated milk.
         \n
        1 cup of ice, crushed.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_drinks_2">
        Boil some water.
         \n
        In the French press, add in one tablespoon of Thai black tea.
         \n
        Add in one cup of hot boiling water and cover with the lid.
         \n
        Allow it to steep for a couple of minutes, until the water changes into a deep orangey-brown colour.
         \n
        Press the lever down all the way to the bottom.
         \n
        Pour the hot tea into a big cup.
         \n
        Add in 2 teaspoons of sugar and stir to dissolve.
         \n
        Add in 2 teaspoons of condensed milk and stir to combine.
         \n
        In a tall glass, add in ice.
         \n
        Pour the tea into the glass until almost full, and finish with 2 teaspoons of evaporated milk.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_drinks_3">nom yen
        <!--        (ice milk with syrup)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_drinks_3">
        2 cups milk.
         \n
        ¼ cup Hale’s Blue Boy sala flavored syrup.
         \n
        3 cups crushed ice.
         \n
        ¼ cup evaporated milk to drizzle on top optional.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_drinks_3">
        Mix the milk and sala flavored syrup with a spoon in a mixing jug.
         \n
        Taste the milk mixture and adjust the sweetness to your liking by adding more milk or syrup.
         \n
        Fill 3 cups with crushed ice and pour the pink milk mixture over the ice.
        \n
        Drizzle some evaporated milk onto the top of each cup and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="Title_drinks_4">oliang
        <!--        (thai style coffee)-->
    </string>
    <string name="Ingredients_drinks_4">
        2 tablespoons ground coffee beans.
         \n
        ¼ teaspoon ground cardamom.
         \n
        Water.
         \n
        2 tablespoons sweetened condensed milk.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_drinks_4">
        Place coffee and cardamom in the filter of your coffee machine.
         \n
        Place enough water to make 2 cups of coffee in the machine.
         \n
        Turn on the coffee machine.
         \n
        Pour brewed coffee into 2 coffee cups, and stir 1 tablespoon sweetened condensed milk into each cup.
         \n
        Serve.
    </string>


    <!--    Desserts    -->
    <string name="Title_desserts_1">foi thong</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_desserts_1">
        20 eggs.
         \n
        850 grams white sugar.
         \n
        6 cups of water.
         \n
        2 pandan leaves.
         \n
        2 tablespoons eggs white.
         \n
        2 skewers or chopsticks.
         \n
        Mold for drizzling.
         \n
        I add 1 tsp orange food colouring to give it a nice bright look.
         \n
        Vegetable oil is often added to the yolk but I didn’t use it this time.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_desserts_1">
        Prepare eggs; separate egg yolks and egg whites and strain egg yolks on muslin cotton.
         \n
        Mix egg yolks together with food colouring if you have it.
         \n
        In the brass saucepan (or non stick saucepan is an option), mix together the water and sugar.
         \n
        Tie pandan leaves and put in sugar pot.
         \n
        On high heat, heat the sugar mixed until boil and simmer for 7 minutes.
         \n
        Lower the heat until sugar is bubbling in the middle then put egg yolk in your mold.
         \n
        Drizzle egg yolk into bubbling sugar mixture, and make about 30 circles, let it cook for 1-2 minutes use 2 skewers or chop sticks to fold and rest on cooling tray.
         \n
        Repeat no.6 until all the egg yolk is cooked.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_desserts_2">mango sticky</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_desserts_2">
        1 cup Thai sweet rice (aka sticky rice).
         \n
        1 1/2 cups water, divided.
         \n
        1 (13.5-ounce) can coconut milk, divided.
         \n
        1/4 teaspoon salt.
         \n
        4 to 5 tablespoons brown sugar, to taste, divided.
         \n
        1 to 2 ripe mangoes.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_desserts_2">
        Gather the ingredients.
         \n
        Soak the rice in 1 cup water in a medium pot for 20 to 30 minutes.
         \n
        Do not drain the rice.
         \n
        Add 1/2 cup more water, plus 1/2 can of the coconut milk, the salt, and 1 tablespoon of the brown sugar.
         \n
        Stir well.
         \n
        Bring to a gentle boil, then partially cover with a lid (leaving some room for steam to escape).
         \n
        Reduce heat to medium-low, or just until you get a gentle simmer.
         \n
        Simmer 20 to 30 minutes, or until the coconut water has been absorbed by the rice.
         \n
        Turn off the heat but leave the pot on the burner with the lid on tight.
         \n
        Allow it to sit for 5 to 10 minutes.
         \n
        To make the sauce, warm (do not boil) the remaining coconut milk over medium-low heat (about 5 minutes).
         \n
        Add 3 tablespoons brown sugar, stirring to dissolve.
        \n
        Taste-test sauce for sweetness, adding more sugar if desired.
         \n
        (Note that it will not taste as sweet once added to the rice.)
         \n
        Prepare the mangoes by cutting them open and slicing each into bite-sized pieces.
         \n
        Scoop some warm rice into each serving bowl, then drizzle lots of the sweet coconut sauce over the top.
         \n
        It should look like an English pudding with custard sauce, with the rice swimming in sauce.
         \n
        Arrange mango slices on the rice and finish with a drizzle of more sauce.
         \n
        Serve and enjoy.
    </string>

    <string name="Title_desserts_3">thong yip</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_desserts_3">
        6 cups + 1 cup of water.
         \n
        10 cups + 1 cup of castor sugar.
         \n
        15 egg yolks.
         \n
        4 to 10 tablespoons of Thong Yot flour, which is a wheat flour and rice flour mixture.
    </string>
    <string name="Instructions_desserts_3">
        Make a heavy syrup from 6 cups of water and 10 cups of castor sugar.
         \n
        Make a lighter syrup from 1 cup of water and 1 cup of castor sugar.
         \n
        Strain the egg yolks through muslin.
         \n
        Squeeze.
         \n
        Blend the egg yolks until they are thick and fluffy; this can take 15-20 minutes.
         \n
        Put the egg batter in a bowl and add 4 tablespoons of flour.
         \n
        Mix well.
         \n
        Bring the heavy syrup to a rolling boil.
         \n
        Use your thumb, index and middle fingers to grasp some egg batter, lift it in a sweeping motion across the rim of the bowl, and drop it into the boiling syrup.
         \n
        Is the batter difficult to grasp? Mix in more flour until the batter reaches desired thickness.
         \n
        When a drop is ready, remove it from the boiling water and place it in the lighter syrup.
         \n
        Continue until all drops are ready.
         \n
        You can make many drops at once in the same pot, as long as you don’t put in so much batter that the water cools down and the boiling stops.
    </string>
    <string name="open" />
    <string name="close" />

</resources>